#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-khoavuong-209b9221b (LinkedIn) www.youtube.com/channel/ UChzdfbUUz\_vtfKJABumICGA (Personal)

Top Skills
Project Plans

# Nguyen Khoa Vuong

MEP Project Manager at Unicons Company Limited Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

#### Summary

Experienced MEP Project Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the construction industry. Skilled in Sales, Communication, Mechanical, Electrical, and Plumbing (MEP), Research, and Civil Engineering. Strong engineering professional with a Associate of Science - AS focused in Heating, Ventilation, Air Conditioning and Refrigeration Engineering Technology/Technician from Industrial University of Ho Chi Minh City.

## Experience

Unicons Investment Construction Company Limited MEP Project Manager
October 2012 - Present (12 years 6 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Unicons Company Limited
MEP Project Manager
January 2012 - Present (13 years 3 months)
Vietnam

### Education

INDUSTRIAL UNIVERSITY OF HO CHI MINH CITY

Engineer, Heating, Ventilation, Air Conditioning and Refrigeration Engineering Technology/Technician · (January 2007 - January 2011)